Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your time
oh!
thanks for your time
thanks
Good work
Thanks for the help.
If you're going to say it, say it.
Get in line.
Come on, come on, come on.
Everybody, line up, line up, line up.
Thank you for your hard work!
First of all, the first live performance with 9 members
How was it?
I don't know...
more united than ever before.
a little bit.
I thought it deepened.
I felt like I could feel the 9 of us
I could feel the nine of us
I could feel the nine of us.
I thought it was a great thing.
That's great.
That's what I wanted to hear.
You know, today...
When we're all working so hard to make sure that we're all on the same page.
You know, when you're all working so hard, and you're all solidified.
I'd like to invite you all
I'd like to challenge you
I want you to try something.
I want to go mountain climbing.
I want to climb a mountain
What?Eh?
Lo.
VT
Yes, sir.
I'm going to ask you to turn this around a little bit.
What?
I don't care who represents you.
Here you go.
Elv.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no...
zucchini
ni
car
me
dare
Ichi!
I dare you!
Get out!
Seriously?
Oh, my God!
What do you mean, "screw it"?
What do you mean "die"?
One, one, one...
Come on!
Idiot!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on!
You're hitting it!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have a question.
What's the memorial?What's a memorial?
The one you take with you when you run.
I'm getting excited about this camp.
Okay, bye.
Wait a minute. Let's hear what it is.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Yeah!
Yeah, it's a liquid message.
Yes, the unity of all of us.
As one.
Connect the baton
We're going to run it all out.
Finish the race? Oh, my God, we're gonna run it.
Yes, yes.
The first project is...
The Liquid Propulsion System.
A great revolution!
Amazing!
Left heart
The first level is
Please take a look here
Tokyo Dome
This class
Yay!
Enoshima, such a long distance
Tokyo Dome
Yes, Tokyo Dome
From Enoshima
Everyone's goal
to Tokyo Dome
I've been there.
How far is it?
You're asking a lot.
Yeah, I know.
How far is it?How much?
42.195.
Uh-huh.
What?
Huh?
42.195?
What would you do for a part-time job?
80 kilometers!
100 kilometers!
About 30 kilometers?
Yes!
Hold on!
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
I want to tell you something.
There is fireworks!
Let's go.
It was the Tokyo Dome.
I don't feel bad.
I can run.
That's for sure.
Let's make that project a success.
We're aiming for our goal, Tokyo Dome.
This is the most important part.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
Santa!
This is tough. It's really hard on my legs.
I hope that by accomplishing this with the 9 of us, we can overcome various challenges.
I want to get to my feet.
Isshin and I have been together for almost 8 or 9 years now, so I hope we can reach this goal with all our hearts.
It doesn't matter if it's not cool, we just want to run through it.It doesn't have to be cool, but let's just run with it.
Oh, man.
Oh no.